Hold on, Seiya. I'm coming. I'm not sure I'll be able to save you, but I'm your friend, so I have to try.
The least I can do is not let you die alone.
The air feels so weird. It's like I can sense that chain destruction thing.
Uh, guys, I don't like this place.
Is this the Demon Lord's castle?
Yeah, we're right in the heart of it. And that means what's next will be the final showdown. There's no doubt.
Seiya!
Oh no! Please don't do it, Seiya!
Omega Valkyriesia!
If you use that move, it's gonna kill you!
Gate of Valhalla!
Seiya!
You broke through my anti-magic field!
A Valkyriesia's not magic. So whatever little barrier you put up was destined to fail.
Harvayr!
Oh... well, Vel'cara! This can't be!
But how? The only thing that can cause me partly harm is cessation!
This must be some kind of illusion, some trick to make me believe it!
Whoa! I thought we had him!
He's clawing his way out of the gate!
No, this is not good!
You shouldn't trifle with me, human!
I'd never trifle with an S-ranked demon lord of Gaea Brande.
But I have considered your responses to this situation.
Try this, phoenix thrust!
So you really does need a sacred sword?
You claim to take the fight seriously!
You still try to prick me with this needle!
Begone!
Master!
Veya!
Eternal Sword EX!
I told you your attacks won't work on me!
Will you foolishly refuse to listen?
No!
This isn't a sacred sword, so how can it cut my flesh?
What is that?
No way!
It's the doll I made from my hair!
This is so embarrassing!
I get it now!
Master used his synthesis technique!
Looks like he used it on the spikes in the gate!
An infernal sword, not of this world.
Valhalla thrust!
You took him out!
Way to go!
You good?
See ya!
It's already getting to you!
Just try to hold on, okay?
Rista, you used some kind of shortcut to get here, didn't you?
Whatever happened to following the rules of the Divine Realm?
What?
Why the hell would you bring that up now?
If you die here, you won't be able to go back home, don't you remember?
That's true, but I still beat the Demon Lord.
You're the most cautious person in the world!
How could you not have figured out how to beat him without dying in the process?
I don't know, but...
Master!
I won't let you die here.
Rista?
You're not getting away with this, understand me?
You already stood us up!
We were supposed to go out and have some fun!
All I wanted was to have a few drinks, play around, hang out at a hot springs in our bathing suits,
and actually enjoy a little time together for once.
Order!
Release all the healing power possessed by the Goddess Ristarte right now!
Ristarte, you have violated the rules of the Divine Realm
by using a gateway to move to your final location.
It's possible our tribunal will strip you of your Goddess Ranking,
and I cannot shield you from this punishment if you go further.
I don't care!
That doesn't scare me!
I've made my peace.
Plus, I'm pretty sure this is why I became a Goddess in the first place,
so I'll deal with the consequences!
Very well.
As long as you understand what's at stake,
I'll grant you all your divine power.
Whoa, so cool!
Rista's really amazing!
Isn't she?
I may have failed you in my past life,
but I believe I was given this power to make up for that failure.
And now, I'm gonna save you.
My healing skill is stronger than the Gate of Valhalla.
Hear that?
I learned from you.
This time, I'm perfectly prepared.
Something's going wrong!
The more you heal him, the worse his wounds are getting!
It's okay.
Because I'm gonna save you.
I promise I will.
Both of us are gonna have a happy ending this time.
Right, Seiya?
Wow, you just saved his life, didn't you?
Think so.
The recoil from the Gate of Valhalla is over.
Master!
I'm right!
Hang on.
I'm still alive, aren't I?
Yeah, you are!
Thank goodness!
It's all thanks to Rista!
It's just like you're a real goddess!
Hey, I am a real goddess, thank you!
Did you actually save my life just now?
Sure did.
It was all me.
Hey, what's the matter?
Hard pass.
Oh, come on!
Don't be so shy!
I mean, after all we've been through together?
We're like the definition of soulmates now!
A little spooch is the very least we could do.
Cut it out, okay?
I have no idea what you mean by that.
You don't have to pretend like you don't feel it, too!
You are so good as I command you to kiss me!
If you don't back off now, I'm gonna punch you.
Wow!
Since you're such a tsundere type, this actually means that you love me, doesn't it?
You only act like this because you're embarrassed how strong your feelings really are!
I warned you, didn't I?
Please, punch drunk!
You think that was a tad excessive?
You do know that if I die here, I can't come back either!
You say that like it's a bad thing.
I should slug you!
Then again, it's pretty impressive that you were able to heal me.
All right, I'll admit you're slightly more useful than a medicinal herb.
Abusive and a jerk, too!
Wait!
Huh?
Hey, Rista.
Do you know why the Gate of Valhalla hasn't disappeared?
Take you all down with me!
Annihilate you in this entire world in one fell swoop!
Judgment Zero!
What was I thinking?
I should have known it wouldn't be this easy.
And that ball of black light has the power to destroy the world twice over.
Everything on this planet will be turned to dust.
That means us too.
This is it.
Not on my watch.
Gate of Valhalla!
Don't do it, Xeia!
Once more!
Damn you!
Beating by a lonely human!
You'll pay for this!
So, is it over this time?
You know, for good?
Now don't get yourself all worked up!
Both he and the first gate have been swallowed!
That thing's talking to us!
The Demon Lord has been taken from this world and thrown into the void!
Time to collect my payment!
The life of the Caster!
That is the cost of summoning me!
No way!
Don't worry, Xeia!
I swear I'll save you again!
What's happening to you?
This is different from last time.
Xeia!
Master!
Oh, no!
He's falling apart faster than I can heal him!
You are far too naive!
It's extremely foolish to believe that a mere human could ever escape the gate of Valhalla's toll more than once!
Shut up, gate face!
Hang in there, Xeia!
I need to concentrate and focus all my energy into healing him!
Why is this all happening?
Xeia just saved this world!
Don't kill him!
I don't care what he's done!
I'm just a servant of the underworld, here to collect payment!
Chain destruction doesn't exist in the Divine Realm, so if we go back there, maybe Xeia won't die for real!
He should be able to go back to his original world if he dies, so open up a portal!
I can't!
Look, if I take my focus off healing him for even a second, he's gonna fall apart!
No!
Hey, Squirt.
Thanks for helping me out with the War Master.
Save your strength!
If it weren't for your support magic, I probably would have been killed in that fight.
But now, you're dying!
If I had turned into that sword, you'd be fine!
You wouldn't have to give up your own life for this!
I'm sorry!
Little bro, now that the Four Heavenly Kings and Demon Lord are history, there's no one in this world that you can't beat.
You're gonna need to work with Rosalie and keep things safe around here.
You can't just leave us, Master!
Please stay!
They never even got the chance to properly thank you!
Stop it!
Stop talking like that!
I said I would save you, so that's what I'm gonna do!
But why?
You should be healing!
Why is this happening?
It's over for me, Rista.
You can't give up!
Don't let it in like this!
I failed you in my past life, but I'm a goddess now!
This isn't right!
It's okay.
You did the best that you could.
But it wasn't enough.
A goddess should be able to save a friend's life, right?
I'm useless.
I can't help you when you need it the most.
I'm so sorry.
It's weird.
This feels familiar.
Like it's all happened before.
I get it now.
It's you.
You're why...
You're why I'm here.
I'm so glad that I was actually able to save you this time.
So you're really leaving?
Thanks to all your work in defeating the Demon Lord, Gaya Brande has been saved.
We should throw a parade of honor and give you a huge reward at least.
Don't worry about that.
And besides, the one who really deserves the praise gave up his life for this world.
Oh yeah, you're right.
But let me say one thing.
He may not have cared about what others thought of him, and he could come off as somewhat harsh,
but Seiya always stuck to what he truly believed in.
And the way I see it, that's the defining quality of a bona fide hero.
It's true.
And everything he accomplished on Gaya Brande was something no ordinary hero could have ever dreamed of pulling off.
For their part in defeating the Demon Lord, Mosh and Elulu, our little dragonkin friends, were both knighted by Rosalie.
I know you're gonna do great things.
Thank you.
Masters save this world.
So I have to do everything I can to keep it safe.
Huh?
Don't worry, cause I'll be washing over him.
Hmm.
Well, that does ease my mind a little.
You really gonna go back home, Rista?
I am.
I can't stay here forever, you know.
I'll miss you!
I'll miss you too.
Come back and see us sometime.
We can go to the hot springs.
We still need to hit the casino.
You're right.
Sounds like fun to me.
You promise?
You'll really visit?
Yeah, of course I will.
Alright, this is it.
Goddess Ristarte.
Huh?
Losing my father hurts.
But your strength has truly inspired me.
I'm not that strong.
But...
I know that I owe it to Seiya to be the very best goddess that I can be.
That's what keeps me going.
Guess that's how I should approach things, too.
I have to lead this empire forward.
I know it will be in good hands with you.
But all I ask is that you make sure to take care of those two.
Don't give them any crazy orders, okay?
I'll keep that in mind.
Now give our savior goddess a salute!
The two of them look so grown up just now.
I'm so proud of how far they've come.
So you're just gonna slack off again.
Seiya?
He's really gone.
I could swear I locked the door.
Locked doors mean nothing to the goddess of opening seals.
Sorry to drop in unannounced.
Ishtar is asking for you.
Okay, thank you.
I'm coming.
Goodness.
Looking a little rough.
Let me fix your hair for you.
You know, if I had to guess,
I'm pretty sure that Ishtar needs to speak with you about opening that shortcut portal
and releasing your goddess powers back in Gea Brande.
Yeah.
I know I'll be punished for that.
I knew I was breaking the rules when I did it.
You needn't worry.
After all, that world was a level S and you still saved it.
I'll try to make sure that's taken into consideration.
Now, you're looking much better.
Honestly, I wish I felt better.
Rista, I really hope that you're doing okay.
Oh, I'm sure I'll be fine.
But I appreciate your concern, Adonela.
I know you were fond of Seiya too, so it means a lot.
Well, I'm way more concerned about you than I am about me.
I'm sad, but it's probably nothing compared to what you're feeling right now.
Hey there, Rista.
I heard you were down in the dump, so here's something that might help.
At least your taste buds will be happy.
I'm trying a new thing with this frozen cake.
You really think a cake is going to make it better?
Have you lost your damn mind?
Sorry, I, uh...
No, Rista, don't force it.
It's so delicious.
Didn't know I liked protein cake.
Well, this one's actually a frozen cake.
Then I guess I'm a fan of frozen protein cakes.
I think you may be misunderstanding me.
It's not a protein cake of any...
Okay, still, it has protein.
Yeah, of course, there's plenty in there.
Gotta build those muscles.
I think if you cut back on that a little bit, the next one will turn out way better.
But thanks.
Oh no, in my opinion, he should add even more next time.
Personally speaking, I can't seem to ever get enough of that manly protein.
You should go back to your forest right now, Midas.
If Ishtar sees you, she'll get angry.
Let me enjoy myself a second.
I was only out here looking to see if there was a hunky new hero, so...
Midas!
Oh, you biddies are just no fun.
Bye for now, Restarte.
I hope you have a wonderful day.
You too.
I really wouldn't worry about this too much if I were you.
Nice work, Restarte.
Really pulled it off.
I heard what happened to your hero, but I don't regret teaching him that move.
That's just what it took.
Guess so.
Man, you really look like crap.
But to be honest, that's a step up for you.
That a compliment?
I'd like to paint your portrait sometime, but only if you promise you won't look like
a kid who just lost her lollipop.
Rista, I'm extremely proud that you were able to save Gaea Brande.
And seeing that you've returned home safe and unharmed makes me very happy.
Thank you.
My feelings notwithstanding, the Divine Realm Tribunal deliberated on your violation of
rules and has come to a decision.
Whatever the punishment is, you must accept it.
Excuse me.
Although Restarte broke the rules regarding protocol, she did save that world.
I ask that you give her success due consideration when handing down the penalty.
I have considered that.
And your punishment will be to save the double-S difficulty world, Ixphoria.
But that's a world that's already been conquered by a Demon Lord!
He killed our hero, gained immense power, and turned the whole place into a demonic realm!
Please allow me to go there in her place!
I will not.
I beg you!
Take heed, Rista.
While on your mission to save Ixphoria, your divine powers of healing will be unavailable to you.
If the mission fails, you will forevermore lose your status as goddess.
But Ishtar, that world has already taken so much from her, isn't there some other way she can atone?
It's way too harsh!
And if she doesn't have the power to meaningfully support her hero, saving a world as far gone as that one won't just be hard, it'll be completely impossible!
I don't see it that way.
In fact, I don't believe it will be impossible in the slightest.
How can you say that?
And what kind of hero could realistically save a Hellscape that's under the control of a bloodthirsty demon?
Please forgive me.
When the second gate of Valhalla was used to defeat this last Demon Lord, it also swallowed up the effects of the chain destruction.
So, what does that mean?
Ordinarily, when one fails a world, they can never return to it.
But...
Restarte, in order to take back control of the double-S level world, Ixphoria, you must summon a hero from this list only.
No exceptions.
The ability levels have been reset to less than a thousandth of what they were.
I think he'll do just fine.
Thanks.
Written at the bottom was something I once thought of as a disadvantage.
Now I know it can take down a Demon Lord and save a world on the brink of destruction.
A trait that kept me alive despite all the danger.
And a mindset that can only be granted through reflection on one's past mistakes.
Outro Music
No worries
Hey, if you wanna win, you gotta play smart
You're not gonna have the chance, the wise will take it all
Let me help me, tell him it's a new toy
So I can't be, you're the one I'm gonna
I'm running away from the world's thoughts
I'm running away from my own
You're right, when all is good
You're right, it's gonna be
I'm running away from my own
We'll show you
Oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah
Black glory, oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah
So,結晶とした光を
今こそ解放する
We'll show you
Oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah
Black glory, oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah
So,逆転行 栄光のSlow
確認と運命を始めよう
Oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah